Yes ICC Lombard please
give your opinion on this chart sir, it came a little weaker than expected, the
result is not very special,
net premium income went up by 12%, profit is
also up by 12%, claim ratio has
increased a little, although there is a decrease in expenses,
see what the charts say sir ICC
Lombard,
okay Deepanshu, this is the chart recently and
when I refer to the move
in the inter market, I refer to the lot of April and March
because the momentum of all the stock
indices is from the low of March,
so from the low of March, the
stock which was ₹1000 has become ₹1400 and right now it is
indicating momentum as per ji, I think the
stock is in consolidation mode, below
1320 would be the range where I think
we
can prefer to buy for once, but no, Deepanshu I think it will
remain aside limited and it is not going above 1360 1380,
on the other hand if 13 20  If
13 10 comes then according to me you
should review it and buy it but more le consolidation
would be n butter but this talk is